{
    "id": "aa5c372ec8ac499a8513a828e6372c29",
    "title": "Simple, Complex vs. Compound",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "That was a sight to behold.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one clause and one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd5cdbacd256450ea5be921d89a92670"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited all of my friends to my party.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one clause and one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "508f7fd2f2704ea0a0a8b8add9f1c35b"
        },
        {
            "question": "What she said didn’t make much sense to me.",
            "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bae48d92c567480a8aca97f40429004c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I invited her but she didn’t come.",
            "description": "A compound sentence has two or more coordinate clauses of the same rank.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "74e4caf6921e4093ae1c61649c20d4af"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got any idea what you have done?",
            "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fee0a5d925e343c0988ee588c10f435d"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took me ten minutes to get ready.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "271000a60cea4460875eb4c2e422fcf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t need your permission to go.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5d84dfa7a7094d05b2c6046d7bdf212a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me if I was interested in the offer.",
            "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f22cf7075244b38bfc469bff06174fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "As I had some work to do, I didn’t go to the movies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e94ba2f55e54b1b81413ae6f35d6560"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was worried because he was guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b803a9c622d464abb245c07bb775ff0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me where I had been.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60b2405edbb846c1bc4956b0ad7d83b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can wait or you can leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5b004d770f124c86b73425a9578f0880"
        }
    ]
}